Today's stage is Komagane City, Nagano
Prefecture
This place is surrounded by two huge
mountains, the Central Alps and the
Southern Alps
Very rare high-quality ingredients are in
season in Japan
Here they are, from Nogizaka46, Nagi In
oue and Aruno Nakanishi
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you.
Nagi is famous for his overwhelming
singing ability from Nogizaka46.
Nagi Inoue is also active as an actor and
model.
Did you go somewhere during the summer
vacation?
I went to Mt. Fuji.
Did you climb Mt. Fuji?
I climbed Mt. Fuji.
Was it hard?
It was hard, but I had a lot of fun.
I went to Australia.
I'm in Australia.
It's a good holiday.
Let's go.
Today's guest.
Let's ask Mr. Atsushi Kozawa about the
ingredients.
It's very rare to find something from
Japan.
Avocado and banana.
I see.
It's a Japanese image.
Wait a minute.
It's rare to find something from Japan.
It's a Japanese image.
What are you talking about?
It's in some kind of dish, so I eat it
without realizing it.
I enjoy the aroma.
Is it garlic?
It's close.
Is it sesame?
It's correct.
What?
Sesame is essential for Japanese food.
In fact, only 0.1% of sesame seeds are
distributed in Japan.
Sesame seeds are weak in moisture.
Therefore, the main production area is a
semi-dry area that can be seen in Africa
and Southeast Asia.
When transporting, the water is drained
to prevent decay.
In the process, the aroma, which is the
biggest attraction of sesame, is lost.
Mr. Tosawa, a master, started growing
sesame 5 years ago to make fragrant
domestic sesame.
Mr Tosawa, who started growing sesame
seeds 5 years ago, wanted to make sesame
seeds.
There are about 3,000 varieties of sesame
Among them, I tried to see what would
suit the environment.
I found a variety called Iwateguro.
It's black sesame.
It's a black sesame variety.
It has a very fragrant aroma when you eat
it.
It's fragrant.
Yes, it is.
The sesame that is very particular about
its taste is the same as any other
sesame.
I can smell it coming out of my nose.
Wow, amazing!
The scent spreads in a different way.
Today, we are going to explore the secret
of the rare black sesame.
Let's have fun!
Aozora Restaurant.
This program is brought to you by Sapporo
beer, which makes Kansai even tastier.
Sapporo beer
Sponsored by the following sponsors
Furthermore
It's really sesame
Using thick black sesame oil
The fragrant aroma makes you hungry
Arrange recipe
We imagine
A new encounter
A new connection
We develop
New memories
A new taste, a new feeling, a new friend,
a new region, and a new view of the
world.
Sapporo beer.
Lemon and life are both strong.
Are you having fun?
It's good because it's strong.
Sapporo strong lemon sour.
Sapporo.
Are you satisfied with non-alcoholic
lemon sour?
Who?
It's strong, it's good, and it's great.
Koi-Shimori Lemon Sour No-Alcohol Greffle
Itadakimasu!
Let's make a smile
Let's make delicious sapon rice
They are aiming at Komagane city in Nag
ano prefecture
Iwateguro is a precious black sesame with
a different scent
How is sesame grown?
What do you think about the field of
sesame?
You can cook it with rice
When I think about it, I think it's like
rice
I bought it because I thought it would be
like rice.
This is how you do it.
It is 700 meters above sea level.
It is a famous sesame field in the
mountains of North Alps and South Alps.
We arrived.
This is it.
Is this it?
Can you look for sesame seeds from this?
Where is the sesame seed?
That's good.
This is something.
There's something inside, isn't there?
Is that so?
That's right.
Is it inside here?
Yes, it is.
If you take this part and divide it...
It's black.
It looks like this.
Amazing.
It's black sesame.
It's packed with black sesame.
There are about 80 pieces in here.
The ingredients that are the source of
the fragrant aroma of sesame
are often contained in the skin.
There are three types of sesame, white
sesame, gold sesame, and black sesame,
but black sesame has thicker skin and
richer aroma than others.
Iwateguro, a specialty of famous people,
is rich in amino acids, which are the
source of aroma, and produces a richer
aroma.
to create the aroma.
I want to plant only good things,
so I'm going to select the best ones.
I'm going to do the same as everyone
else.
Only the ones who win.
I can plant only the selected sesame
seeds in this field.
I see.
So you're going to leave the ones that
have good taste and aroma.
That's right.
That's amazing.
Amazing.
But sesame seeds prefer dry climate.
It's a type of sesame that people like.
It's high in humidity, and the typhoon
often comes.
In Japan, it's not easy to grow it.
When it rains a lot,
and the fields are flooded,
the roots will rot.
And the wind.
If the wind is strong, it will fall down
like this.
It will fall down.
In this case, you can't use the machine
when you borrow it,
so you have to borrow it by hand.
That's why it's hard to grow sesame seeds
in places like that.
That's why there aren't many of them in
Japan.
However, Nagano has the least annual
water consumption in Japan.
Among them, Komagane is the best place to
grow sesame seeds.
There's the Central Alps over there.
That's right.
There's another mountain on the other
side.
It's the Southern Alps.
The Southern Alps.
There are these two mountains.
When the typhoon comes,
the wind gets weaker.
I see.
This is a really high-quality sesame
field.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't help it.
I'm so hungry.
I want to eat sesame.
I want to eat it.
That's right.
I want you to help me harvest before I
eat.
This machine is used for harvesting.
Is this for sesame seeds?
This is rice.
Rice?
There is no machine for rice.
That's right.
Now, let's go.
All the way.
You are good.
Let's do it.
This is so much fun.
I'm scared.
Mr. Inoue.
It's good.
It's true.
It's amazing.
It's okay.
It's okay as it is.
It's amazing.
You two did it in a row.
It's wonderful.
It's fun.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
The harvested sesame seeds are
transferred to the vinyl house
to improve the flavor and drain the water
well.
This is where it dries.
That's right.
This is the first thing I harvested this
year.
I'm drying it here now.
I see.
How long do you let it dry?
I let it dry for about two weeks.
That's a lot.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The mouth is open.
It's open.
When it's dry, the gills open and the
sesame seeds come out.
The signal is...
If you keep it quiet, you might hear a
sound.
A popping sound?
What?
Is that the sound we just heard?
You heard it?
Your ears are amazing.
You're kidding, right?
Oh, here it is.
You're kidding.
I thought I was the only one who heard
it.
The dried black sesame seeds are crushed.
They hit it and break it.
You just have to make it slanted like
this.
Wow!
And then...
Wow, amazing!
If you hit it like this, it will fall
down.
So you have to be careful.
Let's see how they do it.
Wow, amazing!
Amazing!
It falls down a lot!
That's amazing.
After that, they carefully remove the
trash using a machine or an old machine.
Finally, they are shipped as black sesame
seeds.
It feels like we're getting closer to the
sesame seeds we know.
The skin is really thick. I can feel it.
The scent comes out from here.
I see.
The ingredients contained in the sesame
seeds
The ingredients contained in sesame oil
create chemical reactions and produce
that fragrant scent
Now, let's go to Nomizo-san who grows
sesame seeds with a master
First, we will cook on low heat
Inoue-san, you cook, right?
Yes, I do, but I don't cook that much
Do you want to try it?
Just turn the pot like this
Are you good at cooking?
I can't cook at all
Inoue-san, did you cook for the members?
Yes, I came to the house.
I said, there is only one thing, but I
made it.
It's cool.
That's the coolest thing.
He makes it for me.
Then...
It's bouncing.
It's like popcorn.
It smells good.
It smells so good.
It's done.
It's true.
It's amazing.
It's been sold out.
It's scary.
Mr. Nomizawa.
You look like you're playing with your
grandchild.
I'm so happy.
Take out the heat.
The sweet potato is done.
Thank you very much.
I've never eaten sweet potato like this.
That's true.
Seriously.
I'm so grateful.
Let's eat.
Wow, it smells like it's coming out of my
nose.
Really?
I've never eaten it before.
It smells great, but the texture is also
great.
It's fun.
Puch, puch, puch.
Let me try it.
It's so good!
What is this?
The aroma spreads in a different way.
The aroma and taste are different.
And it's sweet.
The aftertaste is very sweet.
Let's add salt here.
The rice made by Nomizo is very
delicious.
Let's eat a sesame salt rice ball.
I can understand the rice made by Nomizo
even if I don't eat it.
It's delicious rice.
Thank you very much.
Add salt and rub it to make the aroma
stand.
Have you ever made a rice ball?
Have you ever made onigiri before?
No, I haven't.
Is this enough?
Yes, it is.
It's warm.
Here you are.
Thank you for the food.
I can see your onigiri.
Sprinkle sesame salt on top.
You are good at this.
Your onigiri is shiny.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I made a rice ball with sesame salt.
This is fast.
The aroma is good.
I'm really happy.
This is a cute-sized rice ball.
The rice and sesame seeds are mixed with
the aroma.
I eat two cups of rice balls.
Thank you very much.
It looks like Mr. Nomizo is crying.
Next is an idea recipe to enjoy the
texture of black sesame.
Mr. Manabu Miyashita is good at it.
I have been running a steakhouse for 42
years in Komane City.
You look young.
I often say that.
What is the next dish?
It is salmon saute.
Saute
This contains black sesame
First, making the sauce
This is Shinshu Miso
This is lemon from Mr. Tozawa
Mr. Tozawa, you also make lemon?
Yes
Why are you lying?
You put this in?
You put it in there?
Wow
This is a luxury
It's so soft.
The sesame seeds give it a nice texture.
I see.
They add salt and pepper to the skinned
salmon.
We don't use the skin, but we use the
skin.
That's right.
We grill it with salt and pepper.
How are you two?
Do you dance quickly?
I have no experience in dancing.
You have no experience in dancing?
You are a genius.
I have a very slow memory.
Really?
It got faster as time went by.
But this girl was very skillful, so I
could remember her dance very quickly.
Did you dance since you were little?
I did classic ballet for about 10 years.
You did ballet. I can understand that
feeling.
Really?
Ballet.
You were good at it.
Yes.
And on top of that, French Dijon mustard.
French mustard.
It's not spicy.
Oh, it's just the aroma.
And add black sesame seeds here.
Here?
Oh, I see.
You're going to grill it from here?
Oh, to the sesame seeds.
That's right.
You're going to grill it and make it even
more savory.
Wow, it smells so good.
And then...
Oh, it's going to be like this.
This will bring back the salmon with the
skin.
So that's how it is.
So instead of the skin, we'll use the
black sesame.
I'm looking forward to it.
Soft.
On top of the plate?
On top of the plate.
Is that okay?
It's done.
Thank you very much.
The salmon satay is done.
How is it? Salmon satay.
How is it?
It looks delicious.
Wow, it's so good!
Thank you!
The aroma of sesame and the balance of
the sourness of the sauce is amazing.
It's like the deep flavor of Shinshu M
iso.
I see. There's Miso in it.
It has a Japanese feel to it.
I can eat it no matter how many times I
want.
That's a good way to say it.
It's the best way to get rid of the rich
aroma of the famous black sesame.
This is the best way to get rid of the
rich aroma of sesame seeds.
I use sesame seeds to commercialize
sesame oil.
I see.
This is the oil.
This is amazing.
It has no roughness.
It's smooth and has a strong aroma.
This is the oil.
I see.
This is Yamada Seiyu, an old shop in
Kyoto that has been in business for more
than 90 years.
Using the old-fashioned way of cooking,
they extract only the first oil that has
a strong aroma and no bitterness.
If you can drink this as it is...
It's the best.
Wow, amazing.
Wow, this aroma.
It's delicious.
It's refreshing.
If you add more sesame oil,
it will stay in your mouth.
It's like the smell is gone.
Only the aroma remains.
What's left?
I can see the scene of sesame seeds.
It's coming out.
The field.
It's smooth, so no matter what kind of
dish you use,
you don't have to worry about it.
I see.
And the next dish is,
Miyase-san, you used sesame oil.
Yes.
It's ahijo.
It's luxurious.
Thank you.
So that the aroma of sesame oil doesn't
fly away,
First, cook mushrooms, vegetables, and
seafood in olive oil flavored with garlic
and
It's so luxurious.
It's done.
Thank you.
The sesame oil ahijo is ready.
It looks delicious.
It's really sesame oil.
It's really delicious.
I love ahijo.
I love it.
I eat it once a week.
You eat a lot.
You like AHIJYO.
I love AHIJYO.
That's why I have a new discovery that it
tastes like this when it contains sesame
oil.
It's very smooth.
AHIJYO has a heavy taste when you eat it.
It's as smooth as water.
Other vegetables and seafood are also
delicious.
It's a magical sesame oil.
Aura, let's go for a bit more, shall we?
Are you sure?
Let's go, let's go.
Because you eat it once a week, don't
you?
Please take it home.
After this, let's have a toast to the
horse-cooked gomadare gyoza that makes N
ogizaka 46.
Let's have a toast to a more delicious
Sapporo.
I drank with a senior I've always wanted
to talk to.
I really don't know if I can do it.
If I can't leave something behind...
My best friend who I drank with after a
long time said...
It's a good thing for Mikami not to be
alone.
Thank you very much.
Where is Yuki Yamada going?
I'm full of things in front of me.
I can't help it.
This is not it.
That's impossible.
There is an ultimate system.
Let's go with a good face.
Ebisu
This is a cancer cell.
If you leave it alone, it will continue
to increase.
Therefore, it is necessary to treat it in
various ways, including anticancer drugs
treatment.
JA's cancer association is a renewal
according to the current cancer
treatment.
A time when cancer becomes one in two.
So I want you to know now.
JA Association.
At JA near you.
Adult elevator.
It is a mysterious elevator that travels
adults.
At that time, there was a samurai who
crossed the sea.
When I hear the word determination,
I think of my family, friends, and
friends.
It's not about yourself.
Even when I'm in a game, I have to be
determined.
I think of my teammates and their
families.
Don't be round. Be a star. Sapporo raw
beer. Good level.
Today's toast menu is made with Japanese
black sesame Iwate-Guro.
What is today's toast menu made with gyo
za?
It's a spicy sesame sauce gyoza.
I see.
First of all, from the gyoza sauce.
Add chopped green onion to soy sauce.
Add spicy chili oil made by a famous
person.
The craftsman makes it based on sesame
oil.
It looks delicious.
Add a lot of ground sesame seeds.
Add a lot of sesame seeds and add sesame
oil to enhance the aroma, and the sauce
is complete.
This is definitely delicious.
At this point.
Add a lot of sesame seeds to the sauce.
There is also sesame seeds in it.
Certainly.
It's delicious because it's savory.
Do you make dumplings, Inoue?
Yes, I do.
Many members like dumplings.
Is that so?
How is it?
We have a dumpling party.
That's nice.
When the dough is ready, they wrap it
with the dumpling skin.
You're good.
It's completely different.
Look at this.
Look at the difference between Miyashita-
san and me.
You're too nervous to put it in.
Is this okay?
No problem.
You're good.
You're cute.
You have a bad temper.
I love water gyoza.
It's good to grill.
Water gyoza is also delicious.
It's a little light.
It's boiled.
Please drain the water well.
It looks delicious.
It's done.
Thank you very much.
The delicious gyoza is ready.
Thank you both.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
ITADAKIMASU
It's delicious
The chili oil is really good
It goes well with anything
We didn't know that it was such a food
I thought that the infinite possibilities
were expanding from here
By the way, it's your first time drinking
on TV, right?
It's rare.
I'm excited.
I'm waiting for the commercial.
Now, let's hear from the two of them.
Nogizaka46, Sakurazaka46, Hinatazaka46,
and Aobazaka46 are recruiting new
members.
If you want to try it, or if you are
interested in it, I would be happy if you
could tell us about this opportunity.
Thank you.
Thank you
I can't resist the aroma of sesame seeds
Please try the precious black sesame
seeds and sesame oil that is popular in
Beijing
Next week, Osechi Kansei Special
Wow, it's wonderful
It's the first time to release the
ultimate Osechi with delicious and
superior ingredients from all over the
country
I'm excited
Who is going to decorate the Osechi?
It's sweet
Kazusawa beef with a sweet and pure aroma
Kazusawa beef has a strong flavor
First of all, it's sweet, and when you
crush it, it has a scent
What is this?
Wow, it's delicious!
This program is
Cheers! More delicious Sapporo beer
We sent it with the support of the
sponsor you see
It's really fun
Ito Sayuri's journey of dancing with a
smile
Hello
Excuse me
Excuse me, I'm from a TV show called La
ugh It Out.
What?
Excuse me.
Are you kidding me?
It's not a TV show.
It's a TV show called Ito Sairi.
Oh, my God.
The whole journey is 90 seconds long.
Thank you.
Please listen to Porus.
What kind of life do you want to live?
What kind of house do you want to build?
Please let me know.
Please visit Taikan Sumai Park.
House Kokumano Curry
Let's order!
You need someone to assist you in your
challenges.
A new challenge for the B-League.
B-Kakushin
The Gizona Group will assist you in your
challenges.
Run with the B-League.
Shohei Otani is an incredible pitcher.
a phenomenal hitter there's no other
baseball player today like him but he
never forgets to have fun keep going
forward prospects